To our grand harvest!
After tonight, the entire Golantis Continent
will bow before the House of Morellan!
But that won't
stop us from celebrating!
So, to every great
house in this room!
Who the freak are you?
Black Dragon Covenant.
Those bastards want to erase
all four families from the map!
They're demanding two billion tons of ore.
Even if I
bleed my mines dry,
I can't pull
together half of that!
They command the most ruthless
Dragon Legion on Golantis.
They've crushed over a dozen border kingdoms
without losing once.
We don't stand a chance.
You're the strongest house here, Morellan.
Tell me you've got
a way out of this!
There is only one
man on Golantis
who might be able
to stop what's coming.
Who?
The Lord of the
Sovereign Sanctum.
The Godfather.
- The Godfather?
You mean, the one...
the alchemists, beast tamers, mages,
and even the Assassin's Guild answers to.
That Godfather?
No one can disturb my seclusion.